{
    "subject": "resource/Eastlawn_Records",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Eastlawn Records",
    "human_readable": "Eastlawn Records is named Eastlawn Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8828641772270203,
            "question": "Is Eastlawn Records a real company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8238740563392639,
            "question": "What might Eastlawn Records specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7851346731185913,
            "question": "What does the name 'Eastlawn Records' make you imagine or feel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7749302387237549,
            "question": "What type of business is Eastlawn Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7725492715835571,
            "question": "If you were a musician, would you want to sign with a company called Eastlawn Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7715184092521667,
            "question": "What kind of information could we find out about Eastlawn Records if we researched further?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6367377042770386,
            "question": "Does the name 'Eastlawn' give any clues about the company's location or target audience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6201788187026978,
            "question": "How might Eastlawn Records be different from a larger, more established record company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22111202776432037,
            "question": "What is the name of the record company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.139461949467659,
            "question": "Can you think of other record companies with similar names?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eastlawn Records is named Eastlawn Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_492_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the record company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_492_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might Eastlawn Records be different from a larger, more established record company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_492_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name 'Eastlawn' give any clues about the company's location or target audience?",
            "html": "dbpedia_492_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_492_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that:\n\nThe triple \"Eastlawn Records is named Eastlawn Records\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON format with my answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four files mention that Eastlawn Records was co-founded by Frank Traum and RJ Spangler, and one of them (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_492/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) explicitly states that \"The name Eastlawn comes from the street in Detroit where Frank's father Emil was raised, as a tribute to him.\" which confirms the name of the record label."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Eastlawn Records is named Eastlawn Records.\" Specifically, the document states, \"The name Eastlawn comes from the street in Detroit where Frank's father Emil was raised, as a tribute to him,\" which confirms the label's name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}